Daniel Bou-Antoun

105 Southbury Road, EN1 1PL | 07948376380 | danielbou-antoun@hotmail.com

Personal Statement

As a hard working, trustworthy individual with a lot of ambition, I am keen to learn new skills and apply myself to any job I am doing. I enjoy working with people and sharing experiences. In my spare time, I like to design and create games. My other interests involve creating short films and animations. My hobbies include football, tennis, swimming and jogging.

Education

- Games Design / BA Honors / University of Arts London (UAL) / Sept 2014 July 2017 (1st/ A)
- Computer animation, Games and Web design / BTEC level 3 / Barnet College / Sept 2012 June 2014 (Merit)
- Art and Design / BTEC level 2 / Barnet College / Sept 2011 June 2012 (Distinction)
- Highlands School / 8 GCSE's / Sept 2005 June 2011

Experience

April 2013 - August 2014

Sales assistant | MBA Furniture

My role included shop floor greeting of customers, discussion of sales options and helping customers with their purchases by processing transactions. I was able to build and maintain relationships with furniture purchasers and kept records of order purchases and contacts using Microsoft Outlook, Word and Excel. I also helped deliver and build furniture in the customer homes.

Feb 2012 - April 2013

Waiter | Sabaho Café

My responsibilities was as a friendly customer facing waiter. I greeted and seated customers, took orders, served food, washed plates etc. and worked on the cash till. I was able to work with a team to ensure a smooth enjoyable visit for the customers.

June 2010 - July 2010

Work experience; Administrator | Her Majesty's Court Service

I had to document and sort paper files such as people's wills. I also organized calendar meetings and schedules, typed documents and completed administrative tasks.

Awards and Acknowledgments

- During my time at Barnet College I was the student rep for my class for three years. I was involved with meetings where I represented my fellow students in suggesting ways to improve and change the college.
- I regularly volunteer to test new computer games. After playing the games I give my feedback and suggest ways in which they can be improved.
- I was paid to give a presentation at Barnet College, to instruct a few teachers and teacher assistants, on how to use OX (the Apple OS) and managing files and folders.
- I have also presented my final game that I created in UAL in a show case in front of some Design Directors and others.